<?xml version="1.0"?>
<bmi>
  <_111>Online business has reached a mark of 70% in the last 5 years. Of all the online business, 90% of them are from Tier - 1 cities.</_111>
<_112>In India, the websites that provide Cash on Delivery service are generally successful. The business that provide promotional offers even after increasing the cost, are mostly successful.</_112><_1131>Cash on Delivery</_1131><_1132>Transportation</_1132><_1133>Limited scope for items</_1133><_1134>Time factor</_1134><_1135>Storage</_1135><_1136>Initial Investment</_1136><_1137/><_2111>Students</_2111><_2112>Teenagers</_2112><_2113>Engineers</_2113><_2114>Rich Men</_2114><_2115/><_231>Teenagers</_231><_423>Teenagers</_423><_2131>Limited funds</_2131><_2132>Parental pressure</_2132><_2133>No COD service</_2133><_2134>Time factor for delivery</_2134><_2135>Quality of the product</_2135><_214/><_232>No COD service</_232><_421>No COD service</_421><_233/><_311/><_312/><_422>Trendy posters in cheap cost and pay through the delivery boy by giving your account details</_422><_522>Trendy posters in cheap cost and pay through the delivery boy by giving your account details</_522><_424>Flipkart.com, almamater.com,</_424><_528>Posters, printing, Transportation, Marketing, promotions, website building, etc</_528><_425>Posters, printing, Transportation, Marketing, promotions, website building, etc</_425><_529>Posters,</_529><_426>Posters,</_426><_521>Printers, Delivery service, Transportation, Online domains, e-banking</_521><_523>We display the available posters in our websites. After the posters are ordered, they are printed by the printer service and delivered to the storage. Then the delivery service collects the posters and sends them to the customer.</_523><_524>We provide high quality and trendy posters in low cost in least working days. We are trying to make their rooms colorful.</_524><_525>We provide better quality posters than our competitors. Once the customer has purchased, we provide some amount of discount in this next purchase, We also do marketing through mails and sms and keep them updated with the new stocks, offers, and new services.</_525><_526/><_527>Teenagers, school guys and girls, people who are passionate about movies and TV shows.</_527></bmi>
